svwh.net 2012-07-30

# Silicon Valley Web Hosting Privacy Policy

**Silicon Valley Web Hosting recognizes the importance of protecting the privacy of personal information about our customers. Personal information includes all of the personally identifying information that is provided to Silicon Valley Web Hosting is sensitive to these privacy interests and believes that protecting valuable personal/financial information is one of Silicon Valley Web Hosting’s most significant responsibilities.**

The policies outlined below describe Silicon Valley Web Hosting policies to protect your privacy. 

**Use, Collection and Retention of Client Information**  
Silicon Valley Web Hosting collects, retains and uses only the information about our customers that is required by law to administer Silicon Valley Web Hosting business and provide high-level services to our clients. We retain this information no longer than necessary to meet these objectives. 

**Maintenance of Accurate Information**  
Silicon Valley Web Hosting has established procedures so that a client's financial information is accurate, current and complete in accordance with reasonable commercial standards. Any request to correct inaccurate information is responded to within a timely manner. 

**Limiting Employee Access to Information**   
All Silicon Valley Web Hosting employees are educated about the importance of privacy and confidentiality. Only those employees having a business reason for knowing such information have access to personally identifiable information. 

**Protection of Information via Established Security Procedures**   
Silicon Valley Web Hosting maintains rigorous security standards and procedures regarding unauthorized access to customer information.

**Restrictions on the Disclosure of Account Information**  
Silicon Valley Web Hosting provides information about customer accounts or other personally identifiable data to third parties only when 1) the information is provided to help complete a customer initiated transaction, 2) the customer requires it, 3) the disclosure is required by/or allowed by law, or 4) it is necessary to process transactions and provide our services. 

**Maintaining Customer Privacy in Business Relationships with Third Parties**  
If it is necessary to provide personally identifiable customer information to a third party, Silicon Valley Web Hosting shall insist that the third party adhere to similar privacy principles that provide for keeping such information confidential. 

**Disclosure of Privacy Principles to Customers**  
Silicon Valley Web Hosting customers have the right to know what information we keep about them and how the information is used. Customers have the right to have any inaccurate information corrected or deleted. 

**Silicon Valley Web Hosting recognizes the importance of protecting the privacy of personal information about our customers. Personal information includes all of the personally identifying information that is provided to Silicon Valley Web Hosting is sensitive to these privacy interests and believes that protecting valuable personal/financial information is one of Silicon Valley Web Hosting’s most significant responsibilities.**

The policies outlined below describe Silicon Valley Web Hosting policies to protect your privacy. 

**Use, Collection and Retention of Client Information**  
Silicon Valley Web Hosting collects, retains and uses only the information about our customers that is required by law to administer Silicon Valley Web Hosting business and provide high-level services to our clients. We retain this information no longer than necessary to meet these objectives. 

**Maintenance of Accurate Information**  
Silicon Valley Web Hosting has established procedures so that a client's financial information is accurate, current and complete in accordance with reasonable commercial standards. Any request to correct inaccurate information is responded to within a timely manner. 

**Limiting Employee Access to Information**   
All Silicon Valley Web Hosting employees are educated about the importance of privacy and confidentiality. Only those employees having a business reason for knowing such information have access to personally identifiable information. 

**Protection of Information via Established Security Procedures**   
Silicon Valley Web Hosting maintains rigorous security standards and procedures regarding unauthorized access to customer information.

**Restrictions on the Disclosure of Account Information**  
Silicon Valley Web Hosting provides information about customer accounts or other personally identifiable data to third parties only when 1) the information is provided to help complete a customer initiated transaction, 2) the customer requires it, 3) the disclosure is required by/or allowed by law, or 4) it is necessary to process transactions and provide our services. 

**Maintaining Customer Privacy in Business Relationships with Third Parties**  
If it is necessary to provide personally identifiable customer information to a third party, Silicon Valley Web Hosting shall insist that the third party adhere to similar privacy principles that provide for keeping such information confidential. 

**Disclosure of Privacy Principles to Customers**  
Silicon Valley Web Hosting customers have the right to know what information we keep about them and how the information is used. Customers have the right to have any inaccurate information corrected or deleted.
